kitco.com 2016-10-26

# Kitco Privacy Policy

September 23, 2010

**Kitco respects your privacy.**

All personal information held or collected by Kitco is protected under the Province of Quebec _An Act Respecting the Protection of Personal Information in the Private Sector_.

This means we will never willfully disclose individually identifiable information about our customers to any third party without the customer's consent. Your personal information will be disclosed to Kitco for the purposes of maintaining your account with Kitco.

**Privacy Philosophy**

Kitco respects your privacy. Kitco does not sell, rent, or loan any identifiable information regarding its customers to any third party. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. When you purchase products from Kitco or register for any Kitco services, we automatically place you on our list to receive e-mail regarding updates about special offers, new products, and new services. If you do not wish to receive e-mail updates, please send an e-mail to [privacy@kitco.com](mailto:privacy@kitco.com) and type "remove" in the subject line. 

**Use of Information Gathered**

Kitco will not collect any personal information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals to create an account and perform transactions with Kitco, or when required by law (such as anti money laundering and anti terrorism acts in Canada, the _Proceeds of Crime (Money Laundering) and Terrorist Financing Act_ _and in the United States, the_ _Bank Secrecy Act_ _and the_ _Patriot Act)_. Examples of such information are: name, postal address, e-mail address, phone number, identification card and credit card information. This information is needed to complete your orders and to allow Kitco to contact you should there be a problem with the account opening process or with a transaction. This is the minimum we need to serve you to the best of our ability. Kitco may share non-personal aggregate, or summary, information regarding its customers with partners or other third parties, but Kitco does not sell or share any information at the individual customer level. Your IP address is maintained for administrative and technical purposes only. 

Please note that failure to provide any of the required information may cause a delay in the approval process or result in rejection of a Customer's account application.

**Opt-Out Features**

Kitco puts control over communications directed to you where it belongs: In your hands. Every time we collect name and address information about you:

·        You can tell us if you don't want to receive communication from Kitco such as email newsletters announcing specials or new features. 

·        You can tell us if you don't want to receive communication from third-party companies who offer a product or service that we think would be of value to you. 

·        You can do this online with an opt-out box when you place your order. 

·        You can stop receiving any messages sent by Kitco by either calling us at 1-877-775-4826 or by sending an email to [privacy@kitco.com](mailto:privacy@kitco.com) with the word "remove" as the subject header. 

**Use of "cookies"**

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Kitco uses cookies only to enable you to retrieve fresh quotes or place additional orders without having to re-enter your name and shipping information each time. Credit card information is not stored in cookies and must be re-entered when it is needed. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use any Kitco site. 

**Security**

Kitco adheres to the highest security measures to ensure Customer data is protected against theft, loss, and corruption, and against the misuse and alteration of any Customer data stored on our servers. We use only the highest industry standard secure server (SSL) for transferring credit card information across the internet. All Kitco employees are aware of our security policies. Customer information is made available only to selected employees who require the information to process orders. However, when a Customer accesses their account via a public or unsecured computer terminal or if a Customer chooses to share their account username and password ("Electronic Identification Information"), Kitco cannot guarantee the security of account data. It is the Customer's obligation to ensure that its Electronic Identification Information is kept secret.

**Change/Update Information**

To change or update your information please send an email to: [privacy@kitco.com](mailto:privacy@kitco.com).

**Contacting Kitco**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with Kitco, you can contact us at:

Kitco Metals Inc.  
620 Cathcart, suite 900  
Montreal, Quebec, H3B 1M1  
Attention: Privacy Coordinator  
1-877-775-4826
